ourawesomeplanet.com 2010-03-28

# OAP: "Our Awesome Planet Network Privacy Statement" | OUR AWESOME PLANET

**

** Information about our Organization and Website **

**

Modern information and communication technologies play a fundamental role in the activities of an organisation like Our Awesome Planet . We are based in Manila, Philippines . 

Our principal activities are: 

  * Provide information on the food and travel secrets in the Philippines. 
  * Engage in eCommerce activities on Shows, Events, Tours and Internet Marketing 

Our privacy policy covers  Our Awesome Planet and its Web sites: 

** Organisation Name:  |  Our Awesome Planet   
---|---  
Address:  |  Mandaluyong Executive Mansion   
City, Zip:  |  Mandaluyong City  ,  1550   
State:  |  Metro Manila   
Country:  |  Philippines   
Controller:  |  Jose Antonio Diaz   
Web Sites(s):  |  www.OurAwesomePlanet.com   
|  www.AntonDiaz.com   
**

**

** Providing Visitors with Anonymous Access **

**

You can access our Web sites home page and browse our sites without disclosing your personal data. 

**

**The services and links of our Websites **

**

Our Web sites enable you to communicate with other visitors or to post information to be accessed by others. When you do so, other visitors may collect your data. 

Our Web sites also include a link to: 

  * Google Adsense 
  * Red Sight Media 
  * Blog Bank 

Such third party Web service providers may collect personal data about our visitors. 

**

Automatic Collection of Information

**

We do not automatically log personal data nor do we link information automatically logged by other means with personal data about specific individuals. 

We do not use cookies to store personal data nor do we link non-personal information stored in cookies with personal data about specific individuals.

**

Data Collection and Purpose Specification

**

We collect the personal data that you may volunteer while using our services. 

We do not collect information about our visitors from other sources, such as public records or bodies, or private organizations. 

We collect name, address, email address and telephone number for the purpose of maintenance of technical information for the website , customer administration and marketing purposes. [ ](file:///Users/anton/Desktop/pwstatement.asp#Table5_2)

We do not collect or use personal data for any purpose other than that indicated in the table below. 

If we wish to use your personal data for a new purpose, we offer you the means to consent to this new purpose: by indicating in a box at the point on the site where personal data is collected 

**

Privacy of Children

**

We do not knowingly collect personal data from children. 

We take specific steps to protect the privacy of children by giving parents the option to consent to the collection and use of the child's personal data for our internal use 

We do provide information about our personal data practices in relation to children on our home page and wherever we knowingly collect personal data from children on our Web site. 

About Google's DoubleClick DART Cookie

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.  

Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.  

Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).  

**

Disclosure and Visitor Choice 

**

We do not disclose your personal data to our subsidiaries or other organizations. 

Where we disclose your personal data for purposes which are different from those indicated in the purpose above, we offer you the opportunity to consent to disclosure.

**

Confidentiality / Security

**

We do not give visitors to our Web site the option of using a secure transmission method to send us their personal data. 

We have implemented security policies, rules and technical measures to protect the personal data that we have under our control from: 

  * unauthorized access 
  * improper use or disclosure 
  * unauthorized modification 
  * unlawful destruction or accidental loss 

All our employees and data processors, who have access to, and are associated with the processing of personal data, are obliged to respect the confidentiality of our visitors' personal data. 

We ensure that your personal data will not be disclosed to State institutions and authorities except if required by law or other regulation.

**

Access to the personal data we may hold about you

**

You can ask us, by sending an email ( anton@diaz.ph ) whether we are keeping personal data about you. 

Upon request, which you can indicate by sending an email ( anton@diaz.ph ) 

We will provide you with a readable copy of the personal data which we keep about you, within a week. \- although we may before require proof of your identity -. We will provide the information at a charge of $10 . 

We allow you to challenge the data that we hold about you and, where appropriate, you may have the data erased.

We reserve the right to refuse to provide our visitors with a copy of their personal data, but will give reasons for our refusal. 

We do, however, allow you to challenge our decision to refuse to provide you with a copy of your personal data.
